嘿
Hi!
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey! - Hi!
-蜜月过得怎么样  -哦  好极了
- How was the honeymoon? - Oh, incredible!
香槟  烛光晚餐
Champagne, candle-lit dinners,
还有银色沙滩漫步
moonlight walks on the beach.
非常浪漫
It was so romantic.
-那  迈克在哪呢   -哦  看病去了
- Where's Mike? - He's at the doctor.
我们在那的时候他都没拉粑粑
He didn't poop while we were there.
很高兴你回来了  我正要你帮忙呢
I'm glad you're back. I need your help.
怎么啦  什么事儿
Oh, why, what's up?
我有个试镜
I have an audition for this play,
剧本要求有些台词说法语
and I have to speak French...
而我的简历里说
...which, according to my resume,
我法语很流利
I'm fluent in.
乔伊   你不应该在简历里撒谎
Joey, you shouldn't lie on your resume.
对呀  你真的不应该
Yeah, you really shouldn't.
哦  对了
By the way,
你在开罗那一年的考古挖掘怎么样啊
how was that yearlong dig in Cairo?
还行啦
It was okay.
我怎么不知道你会说法语
I did not know you spoke French.
你真性感
You're so sexy.
那你愿意帮我吗
Well, so will you help me?
我真的很想演这部戏
I really wanna be in this play.
当然
Sure.
说真的  别再说法语了
Seriously, stop it.
不然我就扑到你身上去了
I'm gonna jump on you.
《老友记》  第十季  第13集  乔伊说法语
Friends S10E13 The One Where Joey Speaks French
-嘿 -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
你干吗穿着我的围裙
Why are you wearing my apron?
我在给艾瑞卡做饼干
I'm making cookies for Erica.
哦  对了  我们得快点儿去机场
We have to leave soon.
她的飞机一小时后降落
Her plane comes in in about an hour.
那她到了以后
When she gets here,
我能不能把你们俩介绍成我老婆
is it okay if I introduce you two as my wife...
和我孩子她妈
...and the woman who's carrying my child?
不行
No?
你要离婚
Divorce?
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你们知道瑞秋在哪吗
You know where Rachel is?
不知道  从今天早上就没见着她
No, we haven't haven't seen her since morning.
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
她半小时前就该
She was supposed to meet me
带着艾玛跟我碰头的
a half-hour ago with Emma.
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey! - Hey!
这些是给艾瑞卡准备的
These are for Erica!
那她也吃不了这么多吧
She's gonna eat all those cookies?
我想让小宝宝生出来
Well, I want the baby to come out
可爱胖胖的
all cute and fat!
艾瑞卡干吗要来这儿
So why is Erica coming to visit?
我们想跟她再熟悉熟悉  还有...
We wanna get to know her better.
她没来过纽约
And she's never been to New York,
所以她想逛逛那些旅游景点
so she wants to see the tourist spots:
自由女神像啦  帝国大厦啦
Statue of Liberty, Empire State Building.
那些滥地方  人总是挤的满满当当
Oh, those places! There's always so many people,
跟牛群被关进栅栏似的
and they're being corralled like cattle.
还有  那儿总是有些傻瓜学牛叫
And, you know, there's always some idiot who goes, "Moo."
要是那这么惹你烦
Well, if it annoys you so much,
你干吗也那么做呢
then why do you do it?
哦  嗨  谢天谢地
Oh, hi. Hi. Thanks for showing up
你才晚了30分钟
30 minutes late.
罗斯
Ross.
不用多费口舌  我肯定你有个好借口
No, I'm sure you have a great excuse.
是什么  美发预约
What was it, a hair appointment?
美甲
A mani-pedi?
还是巴尼斯大降价
Was there a sale at Barneys?{
我爸爸得了心脏病
My father had a heart attack.
在我逛巴尼斯的时候
While I was at Barneys.
-我的天啊  瑞秋  -亲爱的
- Oh, my God, Rach. - Honey?
-我很抱歉  -他还好吧
- I'm so sorry. - Is he okay?
是的  他们说他会好的
Yeah, he's gonna be fine,
但还是打了很多镇静剂
but he's heavily sedated.
好吧  我跟你一起去长岛
Okay, I'm gonna go to Long lsland with you.
你现在一个人怎么行
I mean, you can't be alone right now.
不用了  我还行
No, come on, I'm totally okay.
我用不着你来
I don't need you to come.
我一个人能行
I can totally handle this on my own.
尽管如此  还是让我来吧… 就算是为了我
Still, still, let me come for me.
好吧  如果你真的需要的话
Okay. If you really need to.
我看吃点莫妮卡刚烤好的饼干
I bet someone could use
你感觉会好点
one of Monica's freshly baked cookies.
哦  我还真想吃点
Oh, I really could.
好的  这看起来很简单
All right, it seems pretty simple.
你的第一句台词是 "我的名字叫克劳德"
Your first line is, "My name is Claude."
好  跟我念
So just repeat after me.
-呃  我们再试一遍  -好
- Well, let's try it again. - Okay.
你跟我说的
It's not...
不太一样
...quite what I'm saying.
真的  我听着一模一样啊
Really? Sounds exactly the same to me.
-是吗  真的  -好吧
- It does, really? - Yeah.
-我们再试一遍  -好吧
- Let's just try it again. - Okay.
-仔细听着  -好嘞
- Really listen. - Got it.
-嘿  伙计们   -嘿
- Hey, you guys! - Hi.
给你们介绍一个很特别的贵宾
I want you to meet someone really special.
菲比  这是艾瑞卡  这是小宝宝
Phoebe, this is Erica. And this is the baby!
-乔伊  艾瑞卡  宝宝   -嘿
- Joey, Erica, baby. - Hi.
大家伙儿  艾瑞卡  宝宝
Everyone, Erica! Baby!
莫妮卡  冷静...点儿
Monica. Calm. Self.
-请坐  -谢谢
- Hey, sit down. - Thank you.
真高兴见到你们
It's really nice to meet you guys.
我都不敢相信来到这儿了
I can't believe I'm here.
欢迎来到纽约  或者我应该说
Well, welcome to New York City, or should I say:
不知所云的法语
你干吗要说那个
Why would you say that?
你们今天打算干什么
Okay. What are you gonna be doing today?
哦  我想看看所有的地方
Well, I wanna see everything!
时代广场  科尼岛  洛克菲勒中心
Times Square, Coney lsland, Rockefeller Center.
哦  你知道你该干什么吗
Oh, you know what you should do?
你应该一路爬到
You should walk to
自由女神像的顶上
the top of the Statue of Liberty.
-哦  对呀  我们去爬吧   -太好了
- Oh, yeah, let's do that. - Great.
这个小宝宝得够结实才行
This baby better be really good.
嗨  打扰一下
Hi. Excuse me,
我来看望我的父亲
I'm here to see my father.
我叫瑞秋·格林
My name is Rachel Green.
我是罗斯·盖勒博士
And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
罗斯  行了吧  这里是医院
Ross, please, this is a hospital.
这词儿在这儿是有其他意义的
That actually means something here.
-那么  我们能进去吗   -当然
- So can we please go in? - Absolutely.
瑞秋  我想我还是等在外面吧
Rach, I think I'm gonna wait out here...
我的喉咙有点痒
...because my throat is feeling a little scratchy.
我不想传染给他
I don't wanna infect him.
罗斯  得了  别那么怕他
Ross, please. Don't be so scared of him.
我不是怕他  我真的病了
I am not scared of him. I'm really sick.
镇静剂药效还没退
He's under sedation,
所以他还在昏睡着
so he's pretty much out.
我感觉好多了
I'm feeling better.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我给他买的耳毛和鼻毛剪
That ear and nose hair trimmer I got him
算是白花钱了
was just money down the drain, huh?
格林小姐
Ms. Green?
你爸爸的医生在电话上
Your father's doctor's on the phone
你要不要跟他谈谈
if you'd like to speak to him.
哦  好的  呃  你在这等着没事吧
Oh, great. Are you gonna be okay?
他还不省人事  我想我们没事儿
He's unconscious. We'll be just fine.
好
Okay.
-是不是电视吧你吵醒了   -不是
- Did the TV wake you? - No.
你把脚翘到我床上
When you put your feet up on my bed,
压住我的导尿管了
you tugged on my catheter.
你来这儿干吗
What are you doing here, Geller?
我和瑞秋一块儿来的
Well, I came with Rachel,
她一会儿就回来
who should be back any second.
最近怎么样
So, what's new?
哦  我得了点儿心脏病
Oh, I had a little heart attack.
是吧  疼吗
Right. Is it painful?
什么  你是指心脏病
What, the heart attack
还是指在这跟你聊天
or sitting here talking to you?
看看能不能把瑞秋叫过来
Let's see if we can get that Rachel back in here.
那你最近怎么样
So, what's new with you?
是不是又让我别的女儿也怀孕了
Knocked up any more of my daughters lately?
没有  只有那一个  瑞秋
Nope. Just the one. Rach!
不对
No!
好吧  也许我们应该拆散了试试
Okay, maybe if we just break it down.
好吧  我们试试一次一个音节
Okay, let's try it one syllable at a time.
好的  跟我念
Okay, so repeat after me.
很好  快一点
Great! Okay, faster.
好吧  这太难了  我教不了你
Okay, it's too hard. I can't teach you.
你干吗
What are you doing?
我得走了
I have to go
不然我要拿你的头撞墙了
before I put your head through a wall.
不  别走  我需要你
Don't go, I need you!
我明天就要试镜了
My audition is tomorrow!
嘿  我本来想做晚饭的
Hey. I was gonna make us some dinner...
但是你爸的冰箱里
...but all I found in your dad's fridge
只有培根和奶油
was bacon and heavy cream.
我想我们找到
I think we solved
他得心脏病的原因了
the mystery of the heart attack.
你给你父母打电话了吗
Did you call your parents?
哦  打过了  艾玛很好
Oh, yeah. Emma's doing great.
哦  好
Oh, good.
-怎么  -只是不敢相信
- What? - I just can't believe...
我在瑞秋·格林的房间里
...I'm in Rachel Green's room.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你以前到过我的房间
You've been in my room before.
可不是
Yeah, sure, right.
就跟我真来过瑞秋·格林房间似的
Like I'd ever be in Rachel Green's room.
好吧  我得跟你说
Okay, I gotta tell you,
你叫我的全名可真有点儿怪
it's really weird when you use my whole name.
对不起
Sorry.
-你还好吧  -还行
- You okay? - Yeah.
-今天太累了  是吧  -是啊
- Yeah, you had a rough day. - Yeah.
看到他那个样子很奇怪  你知道吗
It's just so weird seeing him like that, you know?
我是说  他是个医生
I mean, he's a doctor.
医生怎么会得病的呢
You don't expect doctors to get sick.
但我们确实会得病
But we do.
他会好的  瑞秋
He's gonna be okay, Rach.
我不想让他醒来一个人
I don't want him to wake up alone.
我得去医院
I should go to the hospital.
什么  不  等等  嘿  你看
What? No, no. Hey, hey, look.
什么
What?
他服了很多镇静药
They gave him a lot of medication.
他甚至都不会知道你在不在那儿
He wouldn't even know if you were there.
我们明天一早就去看他  好吗
We'll go see him first thing in the morning. Ok?
真的  我不去也不用于心有愧
Really? I shouldn't feel guilty?
不用  天啊  嘿
No-- God, hey.
瑞秋  你是个好女儿  知道吗
Rach, you've been an amazing daughter, okay?
现在  你需要好好休息一下
Right now you need to get some rest.
好吧  也许你说得对
Okay, maybe you're right.
晚安
Good night.
等等...
Wait, wait, wait.
你能不能在这
Would you stay here
陪我呆一会儿
with me for a little while?
-当然  -好
- Sure. - Okay.
谢谢你今天陪我来
Thank you for coming with me today.
哦  应该的
Oh, of course.
瑞秋·格林很高兴你在她房间里
Rachel Green is very happy you're in her room.
我也很高兴  来
Me too. Come here.
我只是不想晚上一个人在这儿
I just don't wanna be alone tonight.
那好
Okay, well,
我可以找条睡袋什么的...
I can maybe grab a sleeping bag or--
不行  瑞秋
No, Rach!
抱歉
I'm sorry,
我只是觉得这样不好
I just don't think this is a good idea.
我们不做怎么知道好不好
Well, we won't know that until we do it,
对吧
will we?
不  你看  嗯…
No, look, uh.
你为你父亲的事儿心烦
You are upset about your father,
你现在很脆弱
and you're feeling vulnerable...
而且我觉得这时候
...and I just don't feel it
这么做不对
would be right.
我会觉得
I feel like I'd be, you know,
这是在占你便宜
taking advantage of you.
什么 占便宜
What--? Taking advantage?
我在主动投怀送抱  你尽兴好啦
I am giving you the advantage. Enjoy!
我知道肯定会很美妙...
Look, I'm sure it would be great...
但我认为我们俩得有一个保持清醒
...but I think one of us has to be thinking clearly.
所以我要走了
So I'm gonna go.
好吧
Okay.
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
我都4个月没有做爱了
I haven't had sex in four months.
我刚才的高姿态应该得块奖章
I should get a medal for that!
谢谢你们带我去了那么多地方
Thanks so much for taking me to all those places.
我玩得很高兴
I had a great time.
哦  我也很高兴
I'm glad.
但是  我得为钱德勒道歉
Listen, I wanna apologize about Chandler, though.
我没想到他会这样
I just did not see this coming.
纽约可真棒
New York is awesome!
你怎么回事儿
What is with you?
你知道吗  我以前去过那些地方
You know, I've been to these places before...
但是我都没有好好看过风景
...but I've never really seen them.
没错  你学牛叫的时候错过好多风景
Yeah, you miss a lot when you're mooing.
非常感谢你们带我观光
Thank you for showing me around.
哦  我们很高兴陪你去
Oh, it was our pleasure.
我们也想跟你熟悉熟悉
We're so much enjoying getting to know you.
呃  你们还有什么想了解的吗
Well, if there's anything else you wanna know....
好吧
Okay.
你不会介意我问几个
Can we ask you some questions
有关孩子父亲的问题吧
about the father?
哦  没关系
Oh, sure. Yeah.
他是我高中的男朋友
Well, he was my high-school boyfriend,
足球队长  很可爱
captain of the football team, really cute.
后来他得到奖学金  上了大学
Got a scholarship and went to college.
那不错啊
That's great.
是啊  差不多就是他了
Yeah, it's almost definitely him.
那怎么说
How's that, now?
也有可能是另外一个人
Well, there's a chance it's another guy.
我是说  我只跟两个人好过
I mean, I've only ever been with two guys...
但是时间上有些重叠
...but they sort of overlapped.
那么  另一个人是干什么的
So, what does the other guy do?
他也上大学了吗
Does he go to college too?
不  他在蹲监狱
No, he's in prison.
那他是被诬告的吧
Was he falsely accused of something?
不
No.
他用铁铲杀了他爸爸
He killed his father with a shovel.
但是除此之外  他还是个不错的人
Other than that, he's a great guy.
我猜他爸爸不这么想
I'll bet his dad doesn't think so.
-你醒着呢吗   -我当然还醒着
- Are you awake? - Of course I'm awake.
从今往后我是睡不着啦
Assume from now on that I'm always awake.
好啦  我们也不确定就一定是他
All right, we don't know that it's him.
我是说  也可能是那个踢足球的
I mean, it could be the football guy.
亲爱的  我们这对儿倒霉蛋
Honey, it's us.
肯定是摊上那个铁铲杀手
Of course it's the shovel killer.
好了  好了  就算是他
Well, all right, let's say that it is him.
我们就不要这孩子了  不
Would we not want the baby? No.
我们会对他另眼相待吗
Would we treat him any differently?
我会一直提防着他的
I'd keep an eye on him.
我们一定得查出哪一个是孩子的父亲
We have to find out who the father is.
-怎么查  -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
这种事儿可以测出来的  对吧
They have tests for these things, right?
是  不过我们也许反应过度了
Yes, but maybe we're just overreacting.
你说得当然轻巧
Easy for you to say.
他杀的是他爸爸
He's a father killer.
他没准儿很爱他老妈
He probably loves his mommy.
他没准儿在挥铲子的胳膊上
He's probably got a tattoo
刺着"妈妈"呢
that says "Mom" on his shovel-wielding arm.
"现在我们从一数到五"
We'll now count from one to five.
-"说得真好"  -谢谢
- Good job. - Thank you.
-嘿  -嘿  乔伊
- Hey. - Hey, Joey.
听我说  昨天的事儿我觉得不太好
Listen, I feel really badly about yesterday,
我想了很多
and I thought about it a lot.
我想是我太没有耐心了
No, I was too impatient.
所以  我们今天再试试
So let's try it again.
哦不  不用了  我不用你帮忙了
That's okay. I don't need your help.
我可以自学
I worked on it myself,
而且我得说我学得还不错嘞
and I gotta say I am pretty good.
真的  说几句给我听听
Really, can I hear some of it?
当然可以
Sure, sure.
好
Okay.
怎么样
See?
好吧  你说的不是...
You, you're not--
你不是在...
You're not-- You're--
我再次重申  你说的不是法语
Again, you're not speaking French!
哦  我觉着我说的是法语
Oh, well, I think I am.
而且我肯定能得到那个角色
Yeah, and I think I'm definitely gonna get the part.
你怎么会这么想的
How could you possibly think that?
至少
For one thing.
磁带上的那家伙说
The guy on the tape
我念得不错
said I was doing a good job!
嗨  瑞秋  给我倒杯咖啡好吗
Hey, Rach, can you grab me a cup of coffee?
当然可以
Sure.
你一早上话不多
You've been quiet all morning.
没事儿吧
Is everything okay?
-你肯定没事  -当然
- You sure you're all right? - Yep.
好
Okay.
好吧  那我去买点早饭
Well, I'm gonna go grab us some breakfast.
有个意见供你参考
FYI.
得  来啦
There it is.
以后
In the future...
如果有女孩子需要点不理智的安慰性的爱爱
...when a girl asks for some ill-advised sympathy sex,
你就满足她好啦
just do it.
等等  你是因为昨晚的事儿生我的气
Wait, wait, you're mad at me about last night?
我只是想做对的事
I was just trying to do the right thing.
真的
Really?
对我来说
It seems to me.
要是你做得对的话
If you had done the right thing...
我就不会一早醒来
...l wouldn't have woken up
感觉又愚蠢又尴尬
feeling stupid and embarrassed.
我只会觉得舒适而满意
I would've woken up feeling comforted and satisfied.
-呃...  -哦  得了吧
- Well-- - Oh, stop that!
我不敢相信  你怎么...
I can't believe this. What you...
我只是做了回好人
I was just being a good guy.
我以尊重和同情之心待你
I treated you with respect and understanding.
啊  那可真性感
Oh, that is so hot.
嘿  我是在为你着想
Hey, I was looking out for you.
哦  真的  罗斯
Oh, really? Well, Ross,
你要知道  我不是个小丫头
you know what? I am a big girl.
我不需要有人告诉我
I don't need someone telling me
什么对我来说最好
what is best for me.
虽说以前我也经常没过成性生活
I gotta say, I've not had sex a lot of times before.
但这次是最糟糕的
This is the worst ever!
哦  真的  真的
Oh, really? Really?
这对我来说也好不到哪儿去
Well, it wasn't very good for me either.
哦  你猜...
Okay, you know--?
嘿  嘿  你猜怎么着
Hey, hey, you know what?
为了以后少这种麻烦
To avoid this little thing in the future...
咱们就干脆说定
...let's just say you and me?
你我以后再也不上床了
Never having sex again.
什么
What?
对了  "性"这个字以后免谈
That's right! Sex is off the table!
我再也不会跟你睡觉啦
I am never having sex with you again!
格林医生  你感觉好点儿了吗
Dr. Green, are you feeling better?
嘿  午饭怎么样
Hey. How was lunch?
我们吃得不错
We had a good time.
对了
By the way,
我想求你一件事
I wanted to ask you something.
这对我来说很重要   如果是个男孩
It would really mean a lot to me if the baby was a boy...
你能不能让孩子  随我父亲的名字
...that you name him after my father...
吉米尼·比利·鲍勃
...Jiminy Billy Bob.
-哦  真的  -不
- Oh, really? - No!
你说得没错  这真好玩
You were right. That was fun.
我要去收拾东西了
I'm gonna go finish packing.
那么  她愿意去做检测吗
So is she gonna take the test?
不  用不着了
No, she doesn't have to.
我知道谁是父亲
I found out who the father is.
哦  上帝
Oh, God.
是铁铲乔  对吧
It's Shovely Joe, isn't it?
不  不是的
No, it's not.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
看来艾瑞卡性教育课学得不好
Erica didn't pay attention in sex ed class...
她跟蹲监狱的家伙
...because the things
做的事
she did with that prison guy?
不太可能让她怀孕
It'd be pretty hard to make a baby that way.
天呐  什么姿势
Oh, God, what was it?
是我们很少做的
The thing we hardly ever do,
还是我们从没做过的
or the thing we never do?
我们从没做过的
The thing we never do.
铁铲乔
Shovely Joe.
你准备好了就开始吧  乔伊
Whenever you're ready, Joey.
好的
Right.
对不起  怎么回事儿
I'm sorry, what's going on?
哥们儿  来嘛  说法语啦
Dude, come on, French it up.
乔伊  你会说法语吗
Joey, do you speak French?
我看这次试镜就到此为止吧
You know what? I think this audition is over.
打扰一下
Excuse me?
我是瑞金·弗兰基
I am Regine Phalange.
我刚路过
I was passing by
听到这个人在说
when I heard this man speaking...
我们法国小镇雅诗兰黛的方言
...the regional dialect of my French town of Estee Lauder.
你真的认为这个人在说法语
You really think this man is speaking French?
好的（法语）
我告诉你真相（法语）
他是我弟弟（法语）
他...（法语）
有点脑残（法语）
你能不能假装夸他一下（法语）
干得不错  小家伙
Good job, little buddy.
你的法语讲得很好
That was some really good French.
但是我觉得还是
But I think we're gonna go with
其他人更适合这个角色
someone else for the part.
哦  好吧  但是我的法语很好
All right, but my French was good?
非常好
It was great.
看到了吧
See?
艾玛睡着了
Emma's down for the night.
哦  好的
Oh, good.
-那我看我该走了   -好的
- So I guess I'm gonna take off. - Okay.
嘿  听我说  你走之前  我…
Hey, listen, just before you go--
我想再次谢谢你
I just wanna say thank you
能陪我一起去看我爸
for coming with me.
没问题
Oh, no problem.
还有  你知道我…
And also, you know, l--
我在想你说的话
I was thinking about what you said,
你知道的  关于性什么的…
you know, about the whole sex thing....
也许再重蹈覆辙确实不是个好主意
Probably not a great idea to go down that road again.
谢谢  我很高兴你也这么想
Thank you. I'm glad you agree.
这也有点可惜
It's a shame, though.
我是说   我们做的时候感觉不错
When we did it, it was pretty good.
对
Yeah.
对  那倒是真的
Yeah, that's true.
嘿  你还记得特别棒的那次
Hey, do you remember that one really great time?
-哦  记得  -你记得
- Oh, yeah! - You know?
那天是情人节...
It was Valentine's Day.
是你的生日...
It was your birthday.
-哦  对呀  -哦  对呀
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, yeah.
我想那都是陈年往事了
Well, I guess that's all in the past now.
-以后再也不干了  -一次也不
- Not even one more time. - Not even once.
不管我们有多想要
No matter how much we want it.
即使我们真的...
Even if we want it...
真的很想要
...really bad.
我们就这么说定的
That's what we decided.
没错
Right.
但这有点难哦
It's kind of hard, though. You know?
是啊
Yeah.
你知道  既然两人有了那种联系
You know. When two people have a connection,
如果不用...
you know, that's--
就好像
Just seems like...
好像是
...such a...
种浪费
...waste.
我讨厌浪费
I hate waste.
-罗斯  -嗯
- Ross? - Yes?
告诉你...
Just so you know...
我们之间
...with us...
那事儿从来也没有免谈一说
...it's never off the table.
可恶  这还拜托不了了
Damn it, it's never off the table.
好了  你真的会跳踢踏舞吗
Okay, can you really tap-dance?
不会
No.
从简历上去掉
It's off the resume.
-箭术  -不会
- Archery? - No.
-骑马  -经常掉下来
- Horseback riding? - Would fall off a lot.
你能在十秒钟内喝掉一加仑牛奶
You can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
这我能做到
That I can do.
得了吧
Come on,
你能在十秒钟内喝掉一加仑牛奶
you can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
好吧  我喝给你看
All right, watch me.
你计时  准备好了吗
Okay, you time me, ready?
预备  开始
Ready, go!
你成功了
You did it!